rugnrug.com 2009-10-28

# Privacy police - Rugnrug

|   | 

THE Rugnrug.COM COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY  
   Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Web Site. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs. 

**YOUR CONSENT**  
   By using the Web Site, you signify your consent to Rugnrug.com's collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
   When you visit Rugnrug.com, you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis, and usage information that is automatically collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web Site. 

**1\. Information that is Automatically Collected**  
_    Non-Identifiable Information_ \- Like many other Web sites, Rugnrug.com automatically collects certain non-identifiable information regarding Web Site users, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, the IP address of your Internet Service Provider, the date and time you access the Web Site, the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to the Web Site, the operating system you are using, the sections of the Web Site you visit, the Web Site pages read and images viewed, and the content you download from the Web Site. This non-identifiable information is used for Web Site and system administration purposes and to improve the Web Site. Rugnrug.com may also use non-identifiable information to initiate interactive, real-time discussions with users. Your non-identifiable information may be disclosed to others and permanently archived for future use. 

_    Cookies_ \- The Web Site uses "cookies", a technology that installs a small amount of information on a Web Site user's computer to permit the Web Site to recognize future visits using that computer. Cookies enhance the convenience and use of the Web Site. For example, the information provided through cookies is used to recognize you as a previous user of the Web Site (so you do not have to enter your personal information every time), offer personalized Web page content and information for your use, track your activity at the Web Site to respond to your needs, and otherwise facilitate your Web Site experience. Advertisements displayed on the Web Site may also contain cookies or other technologies. You may choose to decline cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may affect your use of the Web Site and your ability to access certain features of the Web Site or engage in transactions through the Web Site. 

_    Tracking Information_ \- Rugnrug.com may use non-personal information to create aggregate tracking information reports regarding Web Site user demographics, Web Site traffic patterns, and Web Site purchases, and then provide those reports to partners and others. None of the tracking information in the reports can be connected to the identities or other personal information of individual users. Rugnrug.com may also link tracking information with personal information voluntarily provided by Web Site users. Once such a link is made, all of the linked information is treated as personal information and will be used and disclosed only in accordance with this Policy. 

**2\. Information You Choose to Provide**  
   During your use of the Web Site, you may be asked to voluntarily provide certain personal information (such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, or credit card information) for purposes such as facilitating communications with you, applying for access to certain special features of the Web Site, or carrying out transactions. **It is always your choice whether or not to provide personal information**. If you choose not to provide requested personal information, you will not be able to use certain features of the Web Site and you will not be able to engage in transactions through the Web Site. 

_    Use of Your Personal Information_ \- Rugnrug.com may use your personal information to contact and correspond with you, to respond to your inquiries, to process transactions and payments, and to facilitate and enhance your use of the Web Site. In addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone. 

**HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?**  
   Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our clients. 

   As our client, you always have the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at [ help@Rugnrug.com](mailto:help@Rugnrug.com) or by changing your e-mail preferences in your Rugnrug.com Account Profile. 

   We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy. 

**_Sharing Information with Affiliates_**  
   From time to time, you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on our Web site or within our E-mail communications. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers. However, we cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies. 

**_Sharing Information with Strategic Partners_**  
   We may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties, where we may contact you on their behalf. In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships, we will retain all ownership rights to the information, and we will not share personally identifiable information. **Rugnrug.com does NOT sell or rent client information.** If you would like to find out what strategic partnership areas Rugnrug.com is involved with, you may contact us at [ help@Rugnrug.com](mailto:help@Rugnrug.com)

**HOW DO WE PROTECT AND SECURE YOUR INFORMATION?** ( _Information Security_ )  
   When you send confidential personal credit card information to us on our Web site, secure server software that we have licensed encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. The information is scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches our Web site. 

   Other email that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as account numbers to us through an unsecured email We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction. 

   Evaluation of Information Protection Practices. Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information. 

_    Employee Access, Training and Expectations._ Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions. 

_    Your Access to Your Information_  
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at [ help@Rugnrug.com](mailto:help@rugnrug.com). 

**OTHER MATTERS**  
_    Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information_ \- We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. 

_    Contests and Promotions_ \- If contests or promotions are made available through the Web Site, the applicable contest or promotion rules may include rules regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information. To the extent that those specific rules conflict with this Policy, the particular contest or promotion rules will take precedence regarding personal information collected in connection with the contest or promotion. 

_    Other Web Sites_ \- The Web Site may contain links to other Web sites or Internet resources. When you click on one of those links, you are contacting another Web site or Internet resource. Rugnrug.com has no responsibility or liability for or control over those other Web sites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. 

_    Former Users_ \- If you stop using the Web Site or your permission to use the Web Site is terminated, Rugnrug.com may continue to use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Policy as amended from time to time. However, if you want Rugnrug.com to stop sending you email and other information, or you do not wish Rugnrug.com to disclose your personal information to Rugnrug.com, trading partners or in business transactions, please notify Rugnrug.com at [ help@Rugnrug.com](mailto:help@Rugnrug.com). 

_    Policy Changes_ \- To accommodate changes in the Web Site, changing technology, and legal developments, this Policy may be changed from time to time at Rugnrug.com's sole discretion and without any prior notice or liability to you or any other person. New versions of this Policy will be posted here. Rugnrug.com's collection, use and disclosure of your personal information will be governed by the version of this Policy in effect at that time. Accordingly, when you use the Web Site you should check the date of this Policy and review any changes since the last version. 

   Further information about our complete commitment to privacy and security is available upon request. If you have any comments or questions about this Policy or your personal information, please email us at [ help@Rugnrug.com](mailto:help@Rugnrug.com), or contact our Privacy Officer, tel: +98(711)22 24 376.

|    
---|---|---
